http://www.nukeworker.com/policy/privacy_statement.php

- Search for User
NukeWorker wants to help you maintain your privacy on the Internet.The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live,
and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world--even people you might never have met. It's important to NukeWorker to help its customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.Questions regarding this statement should be directed to abuse@NukeWorker.com.Privacy PrinciplesBecause your privacy is important to us, NukeWorker sites displaying this
privacy statement will operate by the following six principles. Users should additionally consult the Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) section accompanying this Privacy Statement for more information regarding these principles.Principle 1.NukeWorker sites will explicitly ask when they need information that personally
identifies you or allows them to contact you ("Personally Identifiable Information"). Generally this information is requested when registering for
a site, when requesting a particular service, or when entering a sweepstakes or contest. When possible, NukeWorker sites will provide you with the means to make sure that your Personally Identifiable Information is correct and current.Principle 2.NukeWorker sites and their necessary service partners use your Personally
Identifiable Information to operate the sites and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products from NukeWorker and its affiliates. Some NukeWorker
sites may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site's service but are not
necessary to its operation (a "Secondary Use").Principle 3.If a NukeWorker site intends to use Personally Identifiable Information for a
Secondary Use, the NukeWorker site will provide you with instructions on how to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or
promotional mail from NukeWorker sites by following the instructions on the e-mail sent to you.Principle 4.NukeWorker sites that are primarily directed at children will not use Personally
Identifiable Information for a Secondary Use without obtaining the consent of a parent or guardian. When possible, these NukeWorker sites will provide e-mail
notice to parents that children have provided Personally Identifiable Information to the site.Principle 5.NukeWorker sites may disclose Personally Identifiable Information if required to
do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a)
conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NukeWorker
or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NukeWorker, the
site or the users of NukeWorker, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to
protect the personal safety of users of NukeWorker, the site or the public.Principle 6.If at any time you believe that a NukeWorker site has not adhered to these
principles, please notify NukeWorker by e-mail at abuse@NukeWorker.com
and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and
correct the problem.NukeWorker is committed to maintaining its position as a premier site on the
Internet. As our site continues to develop, we may add new services and features
to our website. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Statement,
this document will be updated appropriately.For more information about our Privacy Statement, see the following Frequently
Asked Questions or the FAQs accompanying the NukeWorker sites.Frequently Asked QuestionsDo all
sites on NukeWorker follow these privacy principles?How will
users know which privacy statement applies to their personal information?Do all
sites on NukeWorker need Personally Identifiable Information?How do NukeWorker
sites collect the Personally Identifiable Information?What
about "Cookies"?How do NukeWorker
sites use Personally Identifiable Information?Does that
mean NukeWorker sites sell my Personally Identifiable Information to other
companies?What ifI do not want my Personally Identifiable Information shared with another
company?What about companies that partner with NukeWorker sites to provide the products or
services on a site?What about the privacy of children?Do NukeWorker
sites collect other forms of information about its users?How do I
correct or change Personally Identifiable Information that I have given to a NukeWorker
site?Is my Personally Identifiable Information secure from others using the NukeWorker
site?How else might someone learn of my Personally Identifiable Information while visiting a NukeWorker
site? Do all sites on NukeWorker follow these privacy
principles?NukeWorker is made up of many sites, and new ones are added all the time. At
this time, the NukeWorker privacy statement applies to those sites which display
this statement in conjunction with the privacy notice on the site's Web pages.
While NukeWorker encourages other site operators on NukeWorker to comply with
these principles, users should carefully examine the privacy statements of sites
appearing on or linking to or from NukeWorker which do not display this
statement. Personal Information that you choose to provide to other sites will
be subject to the privacy policies of that Web site.How will users know which privacy statement applies to
their Personally Identifiable Information?Pages throughout NukeWorker display a "Privacy Statement" link
which identifies the privacy statement applying to the site. Users may click on
the link at any time to read the applicable privacy statement. NukeWorker
Websites can be identified by the NukeWorker logo appearing in the top left-hand
corner of the screen.Do all sites on NukeWorker need Personally Identifiable
Information?No, for many NukeWorker sites it is not necessary for you to provide any
information in order for them to provide their services. In other instances, the
NukeWorker site may request minimal information, such as your ZIP code, in order
to personalize the site. ZIP codes allow the site to provide targeted services,
such as the local news or weather, but do not provide the site with any
information regarding who you are or how to contact you. Other NukeWorker sites
need more information about you in order to operate their service. For example,
CarPoint needs your name and other contact information in order to allow its
service partners to respond to your request for more information about a
particular vehicle.How do NukeWorker sites collect Personally Identifiable
Information?Personally Identifiable Information is collected by specifically requesting
it from you. Generally this occurs when you register at a site, request a
service, or enter an online contest or sweepstakes.What about "Cookies"?"Cookies" are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to
your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. "Cookies" can
make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a
particular site, such as your preferred chart settings for NukeWorker Encarta.
The use of "Cookies" is an industry standard, and many major Web sites
use them to provide useful features for their customers. "Cookies" in
and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a
user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept "Cookies".
If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse "Cookies". However, you
may not be able to take full advantage of a Web site if you do so. For example,
the subscription services of NukeWorker Encarta may only be accessed if you
accept "Cookies".How do NukeWorker sites use Personally Identifiable
Information?Usually, NukeWorker sites and their necessary service partners use your
Personally Identifiable Information to operate the site and to deliver their
services. For example, if you are using NukeWorker HomeAdvisor, a completed
mortgage application may at your request be forwarded to potential lenders. NukeWorker
sites also use your Personally Identifiable Information to inform you of other
products or services available from NukeWorker and its affiliates. Some NukeWorker
sites also use Personally Identifiable Information to allow other companies to
contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you
(Secondary Uses). If an NukeWorker site proposes to use Personally Identifiable
Information for Secondary Uses, you will be provided an opportunity to instruct
the NukeWorker site to not allow such contact.Does that mean NukeWorker sites sell my Personally
Identifiable Information to other companies?No, NukeWorker does not sell customer lists. However, individual NukeWorker
sites may partner with businesses to provide special services to our customers.
This type of use of Personally Identifiable Information is called a
"Secondary Use" because it is not necessary to the operation of the
business or site. For example, a site may offer discount coupons for services or
related products. In many cases these discounts would be an added benefit to our
customers.What if I do not want my Personally Identifiable
Information shared with another company?If an NukeWorker site proposes to make a Secondary Use of your Personally
Identifiable Information, the NukeWorker site will provide you with instructions
on how to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of future
informational or promotional mail from NukeWorker sites by following the
instructions on the mail sent to you.What about companies that partner with NukeWorker
sites to provide the site's products or services?An NukeWorker site may have several necessary service partners who assist in
providing the service or product associated with the site. As part of the
operations of the site, these companies may have access to your Personally
Identifiable Information. These companies may provide routine services, such as
credit card processing, or may provide essential elements of the site. These
uses of Personally Identifiable Information are primary to the operation of the
site and are not considered Secondary Uses.What about the Privacy of children?Safeguarding the Personally Identifiable Information of children is extremely
important. For those NukeWorker sites specifically directed at children, and
where users have indicated they are younger than 18, NukeWorker sites will
collect the minimum amount of Personally Identifiable Information necessary to
the operation of the service. These NukeWorker sites will also send follow up
mail to the user's e-mail address instructing them to seek parental permission
for their use of the site. A child's Personally Identifiable Information will be
used for the operation of the service but it will not be used for
"Secondary Uses" without a parent's permission.There are a number of emerging standards in the area of children's privacy
that will affect how we process a child's Personally Identifiable Information in
the future. Through its participation in the Online Privacy Alliance, NukeWorker
is monitoring these changes and is redesigning its systems so as to comply with
these new requirements.Do NukeWorker sites collect other forms of information
about its users?In addition to the use of Personally Identifiable Information to operate NukeWorker
sites, a NukeWorker site may also gather anonymous information, which may be
used by NukeWorker or shared with third parties. This is information which does
not personally identify you, but which may be helpful for marketing purposes or
for improving the services we offer. For example, NukeWorker might tell its
advertisers how many users visited a particular advertisement, and for how long,
so they can measure whether the advertisement was effective. This information is
also used to generate advertising rates. Generally this information is collected
through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies,"
"IP addresses," or other numeric codes used to identify a computer.How do I correct or change Personally Identifiable
Information that I have given to an NukeWorker site?Some NukeWorker sites operate registration pages that allow you to review and
update the Personally Identifiable Information you have submitted. Elsewhere,
you are simply given the option of unsubscribing to the service for which you
signed up. In all other cases where you need to correct Personally Identifiable
Information you have submitted to an NukeWorker site, please contact the service
address published by the particular NukeWorker site.Is my Personally Identifiable Information secure from
others using the NukeWorker site?Personally Identifiable Information collected by NukeWorker sites is stored
in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. In many
instances, such as in the case of credit card numbers, the Personally
Identifiable Information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction.How else might someone learn of my Personally
Identifiable Information while visiting an NukeWorker site?In addition to directly providing information to an NukeWorker site, you
might also provide Personally Identifiable Information through chat sessions,
e-mail exchanges or newsgroups made available to you on NukeWorker. The
Statement of Privacy does not cover this type of transfer of your Personally
Identifiable Information. You should always be careful when distributing your
Personally Identifiable Information in this manner. And remember that online
chat sessions and newsgroup use is considered public and you are responsible for
your actions in these areas.
NukeWorker ™
is a registered trademark of NukeWorker.com ™,
LLC © 1996-2020 All rights reserved.
All material on this Web Site, including text, photographs, graphics, code and/or
software, are protected by international copyright/trademark laws and treaties.
Unauthorized use is not permitted. You may not modify, copy, reproduce, republish,
upload, post, transmit or distribute, in any manner, the material on this web
site or any portion of it.
Doing so will result in severe civil and criminal
penalties, and will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible under the law.
Password Problem?
